Look here.
fast forward
Good morning.
Did you get any sleep last night?
I got a fair amount of sleep last night.
Did you get there?
Nervous?
A little.
I'm a little nervous about a lot of things.
LOL.
Fast forward.
Good morning.
Thank you for watching.
Summer's not like summer... and you don't even know it's there.
The number of times I've been waiting to see the sea people I've bathed in.
Oiga!
ED.
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for your patience.
We'll run together next.
See you again.
See you soon.
I'm coming, everyone!
Three, two, one, GO!
It would be beautiful if we could go for a jingle, jingle, jingle, jingle, jingle, jingle!
In March?
Yeah.
Is it about 35 minutes now?
Yeah. Yeah.
You say you have to talk fast.
I don't know if that's true.
Pretty much, basically, exactly.
I think we did it today, relatively speaking.
I've already got the intro stage.
It's a perfect fit with the chords.Fit by code.
I don't know if it fits.
I don't know, that's where it gets pretty, you know, rushed.
I'd say a little less.
Maybe when you said "heaven of the mother"...
I think there should be a buzz.
Basically, it's the first time for everyone to hear the title.
So I think it's better to have a little gap
I think it's better if there's a gap between the title and the rest of the song.
3, 2, 1 might be drowned out.
There's one more person!
Here.
I'll practice one more time.
Thank you very much.
Okay, if there's nothing else from the members' point of view, it looks like the whole thing is over.
Let's have Justin from the fourth period come up and we'll go after this.
I'm especially okay, everyone.
Okay.
It's the announcement after all, so let's be very cheerful with the echoes.
Yes, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Mmm-hmm.
I think I can do it. I think I can do it.
I'll do my best.
I can't tell you if I can or not.
But you looked good at rehearsal.
Really?
Yeah.
Great setup.
Did you do the interview?
Please do the interview.
I'm performing a new song for the first time.
I thought there was a point in the song where the audience could get excited together.
That's the point I want you to pay attention to.
A sense of fun.Sounds like fun.
What's going on?
It's not intentional.
No, it wasn't.
It just came out of nowhere.
Oh, no!
I didn't do anything.
What's wrong with you?
No, I didn't do anything.
Should I get something to eat?
You can do whatever you want, eat whatever you want.
Okay, then.
I don't eat a lot of timing.
It makes the outfit too tight.
Then speak Okinawan dialect.
My manager taught me.
How's Kana?
How's Hana-san?
How's Kana-san?
I love you.
Do you love her?
Wait, wait, wait.
I already told her.
What?
What did you just say to Aya?
You said that to Aya?
You were talking to the camera.
Okay, that's fine.
That's it.
He's got a fast head start, so I'm not sure he'll make it.
Be careful.
So today is the first performance of the new song.
I wanted to make sure my facial expressions were consistent.
I want to make sure that my facial expressions are consistent.
I'm already having more fun than I used to.I'm hoping to create an atmosphere of "I'm already having more fun than I've ever had before.
I'm hoping to create an atmosphere of "I'm already having fun" rather than "I'm just settling down.
So I'd like you to get really excited for the first stage.
First of all, thank you very much for your hard work in staging the show.
I'm sure it's a hard stage for you.
It's the first time for you to perform in Okinawa.
It was the first time for the group to perform in Okinawa, so it was a very historic stage for us.
I'm sure it will be a day that will go down in history.
I'm sure the fans are looking forward to it.
I think the fans are looking forward to it a lot, so I hope I can challenge it with twice as much tension as I think I can.
I'm also going to perform a new song for the first time.
Let's have fun and make it a good memory!
Let's do our best on the first day!
Okay, here we go!
No, queue, queue!
hard work, gratitude, smile, jump, and do your best!
BONUS TEAM
Let's drink!
Let's all have a drink.
Yes, please.
Hi-Tai, I'm Mizuki Ito from Okinawa
Hi, I'm from Okinawa. My name is Mizuki Yamashita.
It's been a while since I've had that haircut.
I changed my hair style for the first time in years.
I wonder if you guys can find me.
Will you be able to get excited?
It's your first time, but isn't it a little short?
Can we go further?
Yes, go on.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You're doing great. - You're doing great.
Good luck.
Come on, you're gonna put on a little show for us.Look, he'll even put on a little show for us.
Next time, the three of us will try!
You'll be fine!
It's gonna be great!
Come on!
You're doing great!
Good luck, Shun!
Yeah!
Come on!
See you next time!
Enjoy the next issue!
Next time: Shinkansen bullet train Shinkansen bullet train Shinkansen bullet train Shinkansen bullet train Shinkansen bullet train Shinkansen bullet train Shinkansen bullet train Shinkansen bullet train Shinkansen bullet train Shinkansen bullet train Shinkansen bullet train Shinkansen bullet train Shinkansen bullet train Shinkansen bullet train Shinkansen bullet train Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen
Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen Shinkansen
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for waiting!
Finally! I've finally found a new house here in Okinawa!
It's heaven to be alone!
3, 2, 1, GO!
Ladies and gentlemen! Good evening again!
This is Nogizaka46.
I'm Nogizaka46, and I'm looking forward to working with you.
We have just performed our 33rd single, "Ohitorisama Tengoku" for the first time.
Thank you very much.
Well, we have just finished the first performance,
Nagi, how did you like it?
Well, thank you very much.
It was the first time for Nogizaka46 to perform in Okinawa,
It was the first time for Nogizaka46 to perform in Okinawa and the first time for us to perform in Okinawa.
You did your best.
You did your best.You did a great job.
I was very happy.
I was a little nervous, too.
But I think it was a good day.
Thank you so much.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
Seriously?
We're friends.
Well, I guess this is goodbye.
Head.
When I performed the song...
I couldn't hear the audience.
There were a lot of them.
But now
I could hear a lot of voices now.
The reaction of the Okinawan people
I was so happy to hear that.
I was so happy about that
I thought to myself, "I'll do my best.
Did you enjoy it?
I did.